[Music]
i always believe in taking risks and
succeeding
i like to work on my own terms and in my
own way i wasn't cut out for a 9-5
job i went with my heart my family has
always supported me
and given me the freedom to do what i
wanted
i created something successful on my own
[Music]
but today the risks are quite high as
compared to a year back
things are pretty uncertain article
anything can happen to anyone
anna and it's not just the future of my
business
mary family b their future worries me
and now it's my turn to support them
[Music]
i'm looking at securing their future
today
and tomorrow after all family comes
[Music]
first
you